[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けっこんします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "結婚します"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とうろくします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "登録します"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とうろく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "登録"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'つりします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "釣りします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいぎします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会議します"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいぎ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会議"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょくじします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "食事します"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょくじ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "食事"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいものします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "買い物します"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいもの' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "買い物"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなかがすきました' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お腹が空きました"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなかがいっぱい' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お腹がいっぱい"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のどがかわきました' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "咽が乾きました"
    }
]
